Guide to the John Watts Papers, 1945-1982 MSS.093
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Printed Material
  Boxes stored offsite: Box 28 - Barcode: 31142042236508 Box 29 - Barcode: 31142042236516 Box 30 - Barcode: 31142042236524 Box 31 - Barcode: 31142042236532 Box 32 - Barcode: 31142042236540
  - Alcoholism, health issues, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Arts Organizations, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Arts Orgs, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Arts Orgs - Contemporary Music Orgs, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Arts Orgs - Contemporary Music Orgs, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Arts Orgs - Contemporary Music Orgs, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Arts Orgs - Society for the Preservation of American Music, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Catalogs: Association of Independent Composers (AICP), undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Catalogs - Misc., undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Catalogs - AMC Contemporary Music Directory 1975 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Catalogs - Music, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Catalogs - Music, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Catalogs - Music, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Catalogs - Music - CAP (Composers Autograph Publications) by David Cope, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Catalog - New School Faculty 1980 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Equipment - ARP Synthesizer, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Equipment - ARP manuals, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Equipment - EU Systems, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Equipment - other, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Equipment - other, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Equipment - other, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Fellowship in Prayer Monthly pamphlet - June 69- feb. 70, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Fellowship in Prayer Monthly pamphlet - March 70 - Dec. 70, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Halifax, Joan, Shamanic Voices, Book published 1979 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Humor, cartoons, undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Jazz Instruction - text book, undated (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Magazines - Comparaisons, undated (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Magazines - Electronic Design, undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Magazines - High Fidelity, undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Magazines - Music Journal, undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Magazines - Music Journal, undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Magazines - Stereo Review 1973, New York Magazine 1979 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Mail received after John's death - mostly contemporary music ads - Laura's notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Mail received after John's death - junk mail & ads, with Laura's notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Membership organizations - BMI Magazine, undated (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Membership organizations - BMI Magazine, undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Membership organizations - College music Society, undated (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Membership organizations - Mensa, undated (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Music by various composers - published in sheet (standards, Beatles songs), undated (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Music journals - American Musical Digest, undated (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Music journals - College Music Symposium, Spring '79, undated (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Music journals - College Music Symposium, Fall '81, undated (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Music journals - Musical Quarterly Jan. 1952 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - News Clippings - General, undated (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - News Clippings - General, undated (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - News Clippings - General, undated (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - News Clippings- Music, undated (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - News Clippings- Politics, undated (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Newsletters - American Music Center, undated (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Newsletters - American Music Center, undated (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Newsletters - Arts Reporting Service, undated (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Newsletters - CCT Review (Articles by John Watts, Warren Benson, and others), undated (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Newsletters - The Composer; Vols. 1-3 (1970-71), 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Newsletters - The Composer; Vols. 4-5 (1972-74), 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Newsletters - Contemporary Music Newsletter (NYU Publication), undated (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Newsletters - Grassroots Editor July 1966 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Newsletters - Ideas 1952 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Newsletters - I.F. Stone's Weekly (1965-66), 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Newsletter -The Kapustkan Journal (1940s, poetry), 1940-1949 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Newsletters - The New Universe Weekly (1980) (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - Poetry - Merchant, Francis, undated (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - Poetry and plays by various authors, undated (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Press releases for various performers, undated (Box 31, Folder 63)
  - Programs - other composers, undated (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - Programs - other composers, undated (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - Programs - other composers, undated (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - Religious issues, undated (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - Visual arts and literature, undated (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - Sex - adult magazines, undated (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - Sex - adult magazines, undated (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - Sex - adult humor (Eric Idle, Monty Python, etc.), undated (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - Sex - merchandise, catalogs, undated (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - Taubman, Joseph, The Music Business, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - Travel - France, Europe, Canada, U.S., undated (Box 32, Folder 74)
  - Travel - France, undated (Box 32, Folder 75)
  - Travel - Puerto Rico, Mexico, Japan, undated (Box 32, Folder 76)
  - Watts personal items - Historical Atlas and Businessman's Guidebook to Japan, undated (Box 32, Folder 77)
- Series VIII: Photographs
  - ARP synthesizer, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - CCT Performers, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - CCT Performers, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - CCT May Festival, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - MOMA garden concert, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Watts, CCT, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Poster displays, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Poster displays, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Watts Electric marquee, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Personal photos - friends, family, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Personal photos - friends, family, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Business-Manhattan East News - publicity & story photos, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Business-Manhattan East News - publicity & story photos, undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Business-Manhattan East News - publicity & story photos, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Series IX: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries A: Watts - Works on Tape
    [All in white archival boxes except sub-series g, in gray LP archival boxes]
    - Ach Note: 16 tracks Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_1d2828dba3f2448482cd3cdae85a1f70)
    - Ach, Blue Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_206b489c7ebe2a5d7de09229b4932b0a)
    - Ach Note: 4-channel, mix downs Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_3b990a23fe2ab2aec60d1e5876a0ad99)
    - Blue Notes, Ach!, Elegy Note: ARP backgrounds Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_e540c4972bde7721b2c2db614451357c)
    - Blue Notes, Gallery Piece Note: half-track sm. Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_8dd6fd794e72e17d0476f85cf5fb65de)
    - Ballet- NC4 Libra Prod. Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_ad3a7f0a68f259243946a51ca1f146f7)
    - undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_6896a80b738f83e4ef3f7881be98c884)
    - Eutectics, Keepsakes, Gallery Piece Note: ARP backgrounds Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_cc5a6e052ae720356a82a3ad539be9bc)
    - Albright master Note: Do not erase Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_40a5cc398bd96d011e790cfbbb1e0b4a)
    - Halifax-Atlantic City Note: Work tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_e43b0506afedacaaf240d84bf51dc5fd)
    - Halifax-Atlantic City Note: Mixes Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_01fb2a7d1b2172a683adf83ee3240afe)
    - Halifax-Atlantic City Note: Work tape Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_d7229f7e9da793c3a751eded5aa5342e)
    - Aware Week Note: Chimes realization Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 36, Folder data_value_missing_7d1db2d15f6a890ddc3bd75501222f09)
    - Aware Week Note: Master mixes chimes Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 36, Folder data_value_missing_e1e68ece1dcf2713443e076dadf1e0b5)
    - Barbro Variations Note: Radio Broadcast DC 1979 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 36, Folder data_value_missing_01e4c881d645ac3fa076349fa9942101)
    - Bennington Note: Work tape Format: 1/2", undated (Box 36, Folder data_value_missing_ac7d9b531de7d00eb9a14777e048ff49)
    - Bennington Note: Work tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 36, Folder data_value_missing_5e7e22e2c5c543996738985d781d96a5)
    - Bennington Note: 4-track Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 36, Folder data_value_missing_3e47341afec7c17a85300c51a730b34b)
    - Bennington Note: Reference track Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 36, Folder data_value_missing_bf86cbfa5daa801f823e6f9ec72a785f)
    - Blues - mixes Format: 1/4", undated (Box 36, Folder data_value_missing_f095945a4a4ba57e86c2b7a5aff92436)
    - Blues - mixes Note: mix downs Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 36, Folder data_value_missing_2d83937aa770861b9c7db68d2169a955)
    - City of Angels Note: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_3d84bc6d940a9ab865822b39be305651)
    - City of Angels Note: basic tracks Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_d5577b1c7d1ff8515b40052fd0be4fa9)
    - City of Angels Note: master mix with chant Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_d41bedbbacab1d313fd221ff280d389e)
    - City of Angels Note: mono mix with "good news" Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_8d114ba5dc97875d819de6afcf739d9a)
    - City of Angels Note: stereo mix Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_674dcf6bdef38b25a3424938047a0c5c)
    - City of Angels Note: performance tape - Barnard with "chant" Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_508fd87a339a884a3251b1ea691e9640)
    - City of Angels Note: demo tape John and Laura Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_a26d6fb242a396028449172693e6740d)
    - City of Angels Note: demo tape John and Laura Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_13db0f7b82751d4764e494edc8fbe5aa)
    - Chamber Laughs Note: tape II, channels 3 and 4 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_5b4aee3e08f905438643758219882e7e)
    - Chamber Laughs Note: 2nd half of 1969 concert incl. Langworthy, Hellerman, Mason Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_bd4bfb7606c4a07c7b717ffbd9e9c92a)
    - Concerto Note: First Section, plus crude mix Format: 1/2", undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_53cce5e1e2e08f6926988907e23f970a)
    - Concerto Note: Passes ABC, channel 1 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_de71f6c1fc44537f60ef8853cf0c240a)
    - Conversions Note: dance solo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_7eae01bc4bb610ecdcb4fbb810191b5d)
    - Conversions Note: master dance solo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_f3e1552f46be63fd35f9f7a1686ce53b)
    - Conversions Note: old version Brand: Audiotape Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_1e6821932032843cd8c6997a7d7fbf56)
    - Song and Dance Note: tracks I & II, changes/additions III & IV two dubs" Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_92f29dbf0c17a247582ce2f075cc6dd2)
    - Song and Dance "Cubiculo" Note: 10 tapes - work tapes and masters 1974 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_b22091d710ca2814d692e32f414eb07b)
    - Daisies Note: 2-track mix Tarot, Last Supper, Drowning Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_66df5333468f374c58daed7a9e3e4c48)
    - Daisies Note: rock backgrounds Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_257277ee081369b4c26331b573130f72)
    - Daisies Note: III - ending Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_41f26e44ef83ad8924ea6c45ac7a6e54)
    - Daisies Note: opening Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_9141ff086a981c6e6d29e4f5958dd463)
    - Daisies Note: opening, summer island, UR-master Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_ff89c39525f3f4bc5924d3aba9e2f021)
    - AUDIO RECORDINGS - WORKS ON TAPE Continued, undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_12055cff41701d121912b612a27ff624)
    - Daisies Note: Waverly orch track 1 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_852c4bb2a44a7e36284ca2eee424adfe)
    - Daisies Note: Jeff's tape 4 tracks Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_3e7e4f7dd2b5e1f0055cbe36a332b3ef)
    - Daisies Note: 2-track mix; Tarot, Last Supper, Drowning Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_b0fe122b4b9af6d8e3e4af3fdc6a8231)
    - Daisies Note: 2-track mix, takes 1 and 2 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_d89d41825ba8ef8e3b362243df025389)
    - Daisies Note: summer island, clarinet line, funny Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_e5168d7286d393bce9e563e1d4ef4c3c)
    - Daisies Note: 4-track recorders percussion Format: 1/2", undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_cc523c659b10999dce3229d220d0a6d3)
    - Daisies Note: wedding insert Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_f8b0596c20ffa2ed49c071ec25b8e439)
    - Daisies Note: E.H. Insert, ARP pedal, Linda's young lovers Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_97b907e3c79279b56c2e633fabf91167)
    - Daisies Note: oboe & e. horn takes Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_4535d6e4cd7c29c52cd54df57260b96b)
    - Daisies Note: Drowning - ARP filtered version Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_50b6a8d8ee5a2344d3b670349bafdf44)
    - Daisies Opening Credits Note: original 2 tracks Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_957ab5631e08e84e4a2d35a88fab25e6)
    - Daisies Note: no reel Brand: opening credits Format: 1/2", undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_08d8d7f86a30590afefe7bee28b7cb98)
    - Daisies Note: mixed recorders, perc/waverly Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_ccb52b9d8319394b7ec9b0ef95096cef)
    - Dances for Small spaces Note: 1/4 track stereo tape part Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_9f2bb77ad7ce3891bc444fb97ef41b5e)
    - Dancer film music Note: unsync tape Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_0bd9c3a3e8b36e6b5ec0cd33628c3095)
    - Donnez Pas Note: Pig, Roses Middletown II Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_e8f7909f0dc37d4a5aac2fc401696a36)
    - Donnez Pas Note: Noye, Middletown IV Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_371a0b0ab4c201b841321027b3a372c5)
    - Donnez Pas Note: Middletown reel I 1977 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2" (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_fc9a44dca4f42b7118d952996d92ddef)
    - Donnez Pas Note: Roses, Noye, Dr. Fell, 3 pigs, hickory - 4 ch. Format: 1/2", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_45d92dfcf97723a148777a4cefafa97a)
    - Donnez Pas Note: Do not pass go, working tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_d8b12690f34973cb504b7643aef3f0a2)
    - Donnez Pas Note: Reel III Middletown Dr. Fell Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_bb77d4d388398fd1fb5e5d951ff2f294)
    - Donnez Pas Note: Reel III Dr. Fell & First takes Roses Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_3a7a48124e3fcf3497174ec8eeaf3cc1)
    - Donnez Pas Note: Roses,not usable,Middletown V Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_f6f5f2abb63f365154001a1c36a54ebd)
    - Mother Goose Mixes Note: Master - ("$200,000 tape!") Brand: Ampex Format: 1/4", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_6529e2d10a1675813cb3e30845dac5dd)
    - Mother Goose Mixes Note: Master Copy Brand: Ampex Format: 1/4", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_5ee8c44ad99501b448aea30854410cb9)
    - Donnez Pas Note: Master mix Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_d7f9f663dbbe83597e135266eba974d6)
    - Donnez Pas Note: San Francisco State Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_ec2b9c0c37ee0a4906a8d42d584a965f)
    - Mots D'Heures Note: mixdowns from Middletown Recording Sessions Format: 1/4", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_982a83ed102bab1f3822506b870d356c)
    - Donnez Pas Note: background tape ARP Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_2596bae7a8feb050a58fc4f639aa9787)
    - Donnez Pas Note: concert backgrnd tape master Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_7171206728b89cfdfde110e066ac313e)
    - Donnez Pas Note: background tape for rehearsal Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_6b2207ffab9dc558fea82244a4d3893a)
    - Donnez Pas Note: dub 1974 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_7cadb526215e03c7de1d283bb27214cc)
    - Mots D'Heures Note: Background tape half-track stereo Format: 1/4", undated (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_5e391d54920c7ec22cc22ba301cbab41)
    - Donnez Pas Note: Mix for 'Now I Lay', oscillator whistle tracks Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_ebafa681a8e66b99e1e18873bef37c3f)
    - Donnez Pas Note: Rough dubs: Roses,Pig,Hickory Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_8eff465d5f9d764d2327e66b3365cd3d)
    - Mother Goose Mixes Note: non dolby - tones at head Brand: Ampex Format: 1/4", undated (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_0510cfb1778ad7dada9b18bd08da3d0a)
    - Elegy Note: copy I, copy II Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_e65061c8fbda9db1a84edc0e530fd3ea)
    - Elegy Note: backgrnds, raw trks, ABC sets Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_85fdd333314029c81298fdf4ae7c978f)
    - Elegy Note: tape background 1972 4-channel concert copy Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2" (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_aa6e50a2ce21e1a7020bfe5923d08826)
    - Elegy II ("Timeplace") Note: Tracks I & II, original quad background Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_c313e70d30920db8117d1c557eb50fcf)
    - Elegy Note: background tape four channels Format: 1/2", undated (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_18e39557354ad3281033243794e25a40)
    - Elegy Note: Dub made at Hank's Format: 1/2", undated (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_0646942f942e3340b2b85ca7798ca052)
    - Elegy Note: 6 tapes various elements Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_881c77028dc352e772e693dc1fd9ce0f)
    - Elegy Note: demo tape Elegy half-track Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_14a5e758efc0e6f0826e93c59427eb7e)
    - Elegy, Piano For Te Note: Trilogy Records master Brand: RCA Format: 1-inch, undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_1e12de20e915a12318c26ffb0a7ce5c1)
    - Elegy, Piano For Te Note: Scotch Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_d31d8ff05d6e2d5abd07be35f8ab2c74)
    - Elegy Note: 5 Tapes various elements Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_c16a0035262c46dcba3b11248865580b)
    - Elegy, Piano For Te Note: from Quad tape, two-channel mixes Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_24d4cfa52db05a5f84dadecc06d71c05)
    - Elegy, Piano For Te Note: use as masters - Format: 1/4", undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_35a6a69e52cb65fb23389f0d8c18aa73)
    - New School Performances Format: Basf, undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_8898c821bf51389486519509c780d273)
    - Elegy, Processional Note: Concert at FSU Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_dc77f7784fc41cd3daae6bcb229dfd08)
    - Elegy, Piano For Te Note: stereo NAB copy Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_2abae256fd71e0f4ad7ad6df0113a1dc)
    - Dance Duet Note: Practice tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_6ef8a1ca60cff047d120dfe4d8171ee5)
    - Duet Note: old version Brand: Audiotape Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_898725ecc799159f2fd91a96530ec29a)
    - Duet- Del Tredici Note: working tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_d2883074a4add16317232c759d34161e)
    - Entries Note: Work tape Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_613866c168b41d73481422a703e6f006)
    - Entries Note: 1978 tape used in perf. Brand: Shamrock Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_4fe511d1f297e0fb26224ac04b283570)
    - Entries Note: dub Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_dc8b389cdaf1abb686f9771f633381e6)
    - Fantasy Note: 1968 DDTredici mono Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_ea696622023d94cb904c41ad2729063d)
    - Fantasy for Violin & Piano Note: Also pieces by Swift and Green 1971 perfs Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_dab1b9e529c4cb3dc593608d11a3f938)
    - Fantasy Note: 3 tapes Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_6e8791ba8d506a125eb1fedcd0c0a6a6)
    - Fantasy Note: Recorded at CT concert 1968 (demo) Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_536190f2e1820cf5282104178b5f85b7)
    - Fantasy Note: Recorded at CT concert 1968 (demo) Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_efeff0e5c8ba9054d95612596283265a)
    - Fantasy, Chamber Laughs Note: CT performances Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_0892418d325313be51f95eed29a7f190)
    - Fable Fair Note: 6 tapes various elements Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_9526b5a24df9c73c734803c19b9a9ecd)
    - Expiations, Whale dance Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_69b9523a1668365c2fd50f908f9e665b)
    - Evocations, Mosaics Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_b579b37c9d0ca661974cec7309286805)
    - Evocations Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_b23c5d71be16bb1e6f2075a5900cb9a0)
    - Evocations Note: performance Studio 58 Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_c77f8a7f0ebd888617bc8a3c5a749bef)
    - Epicycles Note: sound construction for modern dance Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_4cb6997876979c130fcfa3911873c9cb)
    - Epicycles Note: master sp Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_05d6ae4ac6725538d7184090391a6238)
    - Epicycles Note: Master dub half track Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_c63f49902124a07eb06c0239be9bcb24)
    - Epicycles Note: Dr. Liswood Dub Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_9eba5c3f8871ba640d3e234711215d59)